POLHORODNYK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT



Portfolio website



annapolhorodnyk@gmail.com



Europe



in polllyann

PROFILE

Front-end developer with a background in development, e-commerce and art. SheCodes front-end development certification. Over 3 yearns of experience in ecommerce. Passionate about design and always try to find a best and creative way to solve any issue.

SKILLS

React

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS

Netlify

Git

GitHub

API

Bootstrap

Figma

EDUCATION

Kyiv Academy of Fine Arts and Architecture

2015 - 2018

SheCodes 4 courses

2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Self-employed | June 2022 - Present

During this time, I've designed and developed a few websites, weather applications and dictionary using developers' practices and techniques.

- Dictionary. Built with: React / JavaScript / HTML5 / CSS / API / Bootstrap / Netlify
- React weather app. Built with: React / JavaScript / HTML5 / CSS / API / Bootstrap / Netlify
- Weather app. Built with: JavaScript / HTML5 / CSS / API / Bootstrap / Netlify
- Portfolio. Built with: HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap / Netlify
- Drawing page. Built with: HTML5 / CSS / Netlify

PRODUCT DATA SPECIALIST

LoveCrafts | Feb 2019 - Present

I gained a lot of knowledge about different systems such as Magento, INRiver PIM, Microsoft Dynamics NAV, Prismic, and Amplitude. I've learned to troubleshoot and how manage vast amounts of information in a better and more creative way. I've designed a data model for 3000 products and was leading a QA project for a while.

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING SPECIALIST

Reclamare Digital Agency | Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

I've created tons of images in Photoshop and wrote the same amount of selling and engaging texts for customers from different work areas. I've learned there how marketing should work and how to showcase the most important thoughts through one small post in social media.

WRITER

ArtUkraine | May 2016 - Jul 2016

It was a very short but productive time working as a freelance writer for Ukrainian art magazine. I visited a few art exhibitions, did some photography and research and made interviews with different artists. I've wrote 3 articles about old and modern art exhibitions that were held in Kyiv in 2016. You can read them here.